question_data = [
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
"question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
"correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ", "correct_answer": "False",
 "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "French is an official language in Canada.", "correct_answer": "True",
 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.",
 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.", "correct_answer": "True",
 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "A pasodoble is a type of Italian pasta sauce.",
 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
{"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
 "question": "The Sun rises from the North.", "correct_answer": "False",
 "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
